[{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"How many sales happened last year in the first quarter?\n","engineResponse":{"query-id":"ffeeb3c8-1309-4433-b6b7-f2876c76b973","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.022622417000000002,"error-message":"Don't understand constraint value: subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n of type class com.foundationdb.sql.parser.SubqueryNode also subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n"}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT `sales_amount_local` FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Reporting Year` = (SELECT `Reporting Year` FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` ORDER BY `Reporting Year` DESC LIMIT 1 OFFSET 1) AND `Reporting Quarter` = 1","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT \"sales_amount_local\" FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"reporting_year\" = (SELECT \"reporting_year\" FROM atscaleTable ORDER BY \"reporting_year\" DESC LIMIT 1 OFFSET 1) AND \"reporting_quarter\" = 1;"},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"How many sales happened last year in the second quarter?\n","engineResponse":{"query-id":"1a8be6da-22a8-4540-b55e-df8be2310c9c","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.014777625,"error-message":"Don't understand constraint value: subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n of type class com.foundationdb.sql.parser.SubqueryNode also subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n"}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT `Sales Amount-Order Retail445-30PrdMvAvg` FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Reporting Year` = (SELECT `Reporting Year` FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` ORDER BY `Reporting Year` DESC LIMIT 1 OFFSET 1) AND `Reporting Quarter` = 2","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT \"sales_amount_order_retail445_30prdmvavg\" FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"reporting_year\" = (SELECT \"reporting_year\" FROM atscaleTable ORDER BY \"reporting_year\" DESC LIMIT 1 OFFSET 1) AND \"reporting_quarter\" = 2;"},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"What is the total number of units sold each month over the past 12 months?\n","engineResponse":{"query-id":"5deb0010-a765-4284-9c53-dce8f358b29d","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.015102667,"error-message":"Encountered \" \"group\" \"GROUP \"\" at line 1, column 218.\nWas expecting one of:\n    \"and\" ...\n    \"collate\" ...\n    \"is\" ...\n    \"or\" ...\n    "}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT `Reporting Month`, SUM(`Order Quantity Long`) FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Reporting Month` >= date_trunc('`Month`', current_date) - interval '12 `Month`' GROUP BY `Reporting Month` ORDER BY `Reporting Month`","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT \"reporting_month\", SUM(\"order_quantity_long\") FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"reporting_month\" >= date_trunc('month', current_date) - interval '12 month' GROUP BY \"reporting_month\" ORDER BY \"reporting_month\";"},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"Which month had the highest sales volume in terms of units over the last 3 years?\n","engineResponse":{"query-id":"14bd7c74-b534-4f16-9045-46e8a490cc62","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.071680625,"error-message":"Don't understand constraint value: subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n of type class com.foundationdb.sql.parser.SubqueryNode also subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n"}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT `Month`, `Order Quantity Long` FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Year` >= (SELECT EXTRACT(YEAR FROM CURRENT_DATE) - 3) ORDER BY `Order Quantity Long` DESC LIMIT 1","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT \"month\", \"order_quantity_long\" FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"year\" >= (SELECT EXTRACT(YEAR FROM CURRENT_DATE) - 3) ORDER BY \"order_quantity_long\" DESC LIMIT 1;"},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"What is the total revenue generated by each product category in the last quarter?\n","engineResponse":{"query-id":"34250709-2ea0-4b04-bc6a-a74aad111c08","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.009148375,"error-message":"Don't understand constraint value: subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n of type class com.foundationdb.sql.parser.SubqueryNode also subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n"}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT `Category`, SUM(`sales_amount_local`) FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Reporting Quarter` = (SELECT MAX(`Reporting Quarter`) FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall`) GROUP BY `Category`","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT \"category\", SUM(\"sales_amount_local\") FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"reporting_quarter\" = (SELECT MAX(\"reporting_quarter\") FROM atscaleTable) GROUP BY \"category\""},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"What was the total sales generated by each unit category in the last quarter?","engineResponse":{"query-id":"caa52125-7c3a-407a-8ce6-0d4ceeeca19e","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.01915675,"error-message":"Don't understand constraint value: subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n of type class com.foundationdb.sql.parser.SubqueryNode also subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n"}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT `Category`, `sales_amount_local` FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Reporting Quarter` = (SELECT MAX(`Reporting Quarter`) FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall`)","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT \"category\", \"sales_amount_local\" FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"reporting_quarter\" = (SELECT MAX(\"reporting_quarter\") FROM atscaleTable);"},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"How many units were sold in each region last year?\n","engineResponse":{"query-id":"8b458e8b-f693-451c-a824-4eda147863f9","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.034387,"error-message":"Don't understand constraint value: subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n of type class com.foundationdb.sql.parser.SubqueryNode also subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n"}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT `Customer State-Province`, `Order Quantity Long` FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Reporting Year` = (SELECT MAX(`Reporting Year`) FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall`)","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT \"customer_state_province\", \"order_quantity_long\" FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"reporting_year\" = (SELECT MAX(\"reporting_year\") FROM atscaleTable);"},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"What was the average unit price for each product category last month?\n","engineResponse":{"query-id":"084e816b-abbd-485e-a410-1ad76124bc39","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.014208792000000001,"error-message":"Don't understand constraint value: subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n of type class com.foundationdb.sql.parser.SubqueryNode also subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n"}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT `Category`, `Unit Price Discount Percent` FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Reporting Month` = (SELECT MAX(`Reporting Month`) FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall`)","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT \"category\", \"unit_price_discount_percent\" FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"reporting_month\" = (SELECT MAX(\"reporting_month\") FROM atscaleTable);"},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"how many bikes were sold in the last quarter","engineResponse":{"query-id":"f5ac8fc0-a998-4c39-a23e-128b66307d2c","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.014224209000000002,"error-message":"Don't understand constraint value: subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n of type class com.foundationdb.sql.parser.SubqueryNode also subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n"}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT `Order Quantity Long` FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Reporting Quarter` = (SELECT MAX(`Reporting Quarter`) FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall`)","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT \"order_quantity_long\" FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"reporting_quarter\" = (SELECT MAX(\"reporting_quarter\") FROM atscaleTable);"},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"What was the average price of units over the last year","engineResponse":{"query-id":"fe060df2-de05-450b-9e09-8958a8ed0657","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.010322042,"error-message":"Don't understand constraint value: subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n of type class com.foundationdb.sql.parser.SubqueryNode also subqueryType: EXPRESSION\ntype: null\n"}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT AVG(`Unit Price Discount Percent`) FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Ship.Year` = (SELECT MAX(`Ship.Year`) FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall`)","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT AVG(\"unit_price_discount_percent\") FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"ship_year\" = (SELECT MAX(\"ship_year\") FROM atscaleTable);"},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"How much, net, was sold of bikes and clothing","engineResponse":{"query-id":"3c14b3ab-3fc9-4911-96a3-b976e0768e30","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.019834458000000003,"error-message":"Unknown column [sales_amount_local]"}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT `Product `, `sales_amount_local` FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Product ` IN ('bikes', 'clothing')","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT \"product_\", \"sales_amount_local\" FROM atscaleTable WHERE \"product_\" IN ('bikes', 'clothing');"},{"modelName":"ASAdventureSmall","catalogName":"AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main","userQuestion":"How many times did we sell more than 40000","engineResponse":{"query-id":"386f742f-753f-4ca8-90e7-334204cd01ea","metadata":{"succeeded":false,"wall-time":0.42313900000000004,"error-message":"SQL compilation error:\nsyntax error line 2 at position 0 unexpected 'FROM'."}},"inboundQuery":"SELECT * FROM `AdventureWorksDW2012Multidimensional-Handmade_main`.`ASAdventureSmall` WHERE `Sales Amount-Order Retail445-30PrdMvAvg` > 40000","cleanedUpSql":"SELECT * FROM atscaleTable WHERE sales_amount_order_retail445_30prdmvavg > 40000"}]